Open up the door to the heavy heat A jungle canopy
right above the street The acrylic highway
running on the wall Watching the isopods never
take a fall 200 gallons in the basin below
Keeping the rhythm of the water flow We built an
ecosystem perfectly contained A strictly
regulated climate where the chaos is chained
But we have a single rule for the sanctuary space
A non-negotiable boundary for the human race No
serpents in the garden, no snakes in the tree The
VIP has a boundary and we guarantee You can ask
the insurance if you wanna know why But the
perimeter is locked and the limits apply
Welcome to the vivarium Watch your step
Watch your step. Up in the canopy the admiral
stands Waiting for the tongs in the cis admins
hands He opens up his jaw to show the black inside
A territorial king with nowhere to hide He
screams through the drywall in the middle of the
night Starting up an acoustic cross-species
fight the huskies in the hallway pacing on the
floor totally predictable beautiful war we
built an ecosystem perfectly contained a
strictly regulated climate where the chaos is
chained but we have a single rule for the
sanctuary space a non-negotiable boundary for
the human race no serpents in the garden No
snakes in the tree, the VIP has a boundary and we
guarantee. You can ask the insurance if you
wanna know why, but the perimeter is locked and
the limits apply. Welcome to the vivarium,
watch your step.
The transactional loyalty of the feeding time
The humidity rises, the temperature climbs
The ecosystem runs on a synchronized beat
A safe little jungle at the end of the street
No serpents in the garden, no snakes in the tree
The VIP has a boundary and we guarantee You can
ask the insurance if you wanna know why But the
perimeter is locked and the limits apply
Welcome to the vivarium
Ooh, 2K, no snakes allowed.